This project contains all the tables, stored procedure code.
In order to publish the assets to SQL please open the Publish/TwitterApp.UserData.publish and modify your to your own settings.

The file Scripts/Script.PostDeployment.sql contains the lines to execute just after the publish operation. By default there is one user and password (Administrator role)
User: aldo.sandoval@ymail.com
Password: ABairesdev@1